[{"answer": " Are you all right", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, I haven't seen your baseball. Jeez, my friend, you know you're not supposed to leave the yard by yourself", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Just relax, dear. Now, um...what exactly are we looking at here", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " I mean is it...is it...", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Now I've seen it all. What the hell were you thinking", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Is that bubble what I think it is", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know, maybe you could poke around for a half day and see if she has five kids and a that place", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You don't buy what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Look, let's forget it. Let's forget the whole thing", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " You get fifty a day, period. It's a business trip, they'll pay for your expenses", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend you dog", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " You hot shit. Ya look fuckin' pisser", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Fuckin' animals. Hey, what do you say we go grab a couple drinks", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yeah, and you don't drink any less, right", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Huh", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Three different guys", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well I think you're right, I should look her up", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "But you said she was a sparkplug...", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend? Are you nuts", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I said buttplug. She's heinous", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "That's it, I'm making an oath. I'll never procrastinate about anything again. Life is too fucking short", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " What's that, my friend? What's the bright side", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Don't you want to know my name", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " How'd you know that", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " U", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yeah, that's more or less what the others said, too. Out getting coffee...supposed to meet him here...picking up my grandma..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " I don't know. He's kind of a mook", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " You know, a mookalone, a schlep", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I know he's around here someplace", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "We just got here thirty seconds ago. Isn't this stuff great", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Mainly I work out of that place", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yes yes, I did get my degree up there", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Absolutely! I was there twice last year. Which building is yours", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Did you build the Estadio Olympico", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "So..", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I guess", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Jesus Christ you're right", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " Holy shit, I've been going out with a loaded gun", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " I'm a phon", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I mean I'm a fucking fraud. I'm no architect. Don't be a put", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Oh yeah, the plan was going along just fine until you showed up", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What line? The day you first laid your oily rap on my future wife you started a war", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "You're a sick man, you know that", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Your turn", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well you didn't have to blow us both out of the water. Jesus Christ, just because she found out about you, why'd you have to take me down with you", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I'm talking about the letter, asshole", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Like I'm going to try to figure out a guy who's idea of courting is blowing farts in the chick's fac", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Don't flatter yoursel", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " my friend...", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "But I think I'd be happiest...with you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": " Get over here", "docId": "There_s-Something-About-Mary.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Really", "qsentId": 52}]